export const QuestionData = [
    {
        question: "50 times of 8 is equal to:",
        options:[ "80", "400", "800", "4000"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "110 divided by 10 is:",
        options: ["11", "10", "5", "None of these"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the next prime number after 5?",
        options: ["6", "7", "9", "11"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the answer of 162 รท 3?",
        options: ["22", "55", "54", "64"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Determine the median of the following numbers: 6, 5, 8, 7, 9.",
        options: ["8", "5", "6", "7"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What does A.I. stand for?",
        options: ["Anti intellectual", "Automatic intelligent","Artificial intelligence", "Non of these"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Rational number is represented by_____.",
        options: ["R", "Z", "N", "Q"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "An integer number that is divisible by 2 is called",
        options: ["Natural Number","Even Number", "Odd Number", "Whole Number"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Forming of Association in India is ",
        options:["Legal Right", "Illegal Right", "Natural Right", "Fundamental Right"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the given vitamins is responsible for blood clotting?",
        options: ["Vitamin A", "Vitamin B", "Vitamin K", "Vitamin D"],
        answer: 3
    }
];